Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends III Lord General
Insurance has presented its March quarter
financial results. In today's
video we will analyse
both the quarter ended and financial ended
results which are out. Apart from this, the company has
also recommended a final dividend of ₹ per equity share which will be
approved in the Annual General Meeting. So
now let's move on to the company's
financial results which guys we have
come to, the numbers are in lakhs. Talking about income, the
total income this time was
551, sorry here the numbers are in lakhs and the
income is
516175 of ₹3 crores and in the March 23 quarter the
income is 5255 of ₹5 crores. There is an
increase in quarter on quarter but year on year
income has seen a decline. The
expenditure of the company was ₹4600 crores, ₹
4587 crores in the previous quarter and ₹
3976.8 crores in the March 23 quarter  There was an
expense, expenses have
also increased quarter on quarter but
expenses have increased a lot in year on year
whereas income is down after which the
operating profit of the company is there. If
seen here, the operating profit before tax is
67.7 crores, in the last quarter it was 5737
crores and in the March 23 quarter it is 5725
crores. Operating profit increased quarter on
quarter year on year.
See, the income was down year on year but there was
an improvement in profit and this profit has
improved because if you look at the company this
time, the funds of the policy holders were
transferred to the company worth 561 crores in the
last year, which means that 1278 crores were
transferred and due to this reason, guys, a
good growth is being seen in the profit of the company. If
you look at the income from investment also, it is 233 crores
whereas it is much more than last year
and due to this the profit has improved.
Net profit  The profit is Rs 5195 crore, Rs
4314 crore in the last quarter and Rs
4369 crore in the March 23 quarter. There has been an
increase in quarter on quarter year on year. EPS is
0.47, there has been an increase in both quarter on quarter and year on year. So
if the result of the company is seen, then the
company has presented a very good result. There is just a slight down in the year on year income,
but the profit has a very
good growth. And here if we
talk about the financial year end date, then the
income is Rs
1975 crore, last year the
income is Rs 18947 crore, which has been seen increasing. The
total expenses of the company are Rs
7846 crore. In 23, there was an
expense of Rs 15712 p.6 crore. The
expenses also increased
according to the income, after which the operating profit of the
company is Rs
2555 crore. This time the operating profit in the last quarter of 21 is Rs 122.5
crore, which is a very  There
is good growth, net profit is Rs 191.5 crore,
profit in 23 is Rs 1729 crore, which has
seen improvement, EPS has
increased from 38.7 crore in 23, so
if we look at the results of the company, then it has
presented very strong results, be it
quarter ended or financial year ended,
very good results have been presented, apart from this, the
company has also recommended a final dividend of Rs. per equity share,
which will be
approved in the Annual General Meeting
and if this is considered, then the
company has presented very good results,
which will get positive market response, its shares can
see a rise, hence if
you want to invest in its shares, then
you can enter it now, if
you have entered it and
want to hold it, you can also hold it for the long term, the
company has presented very good
results, so now we
end the video here, if you have any
doubt, let me know in the comment box,
next video  Mein la day ba bye